Benjamin Chaplin Kamas, UT 84036 bchaplin525@gmail.com (440) 251- 8038 Github: Plaindemon

Education

Certificate of Completion

Full Stack Web Development University of Utah - SLC, UT August 2021 to March 2022

Bachelor's in Science

Utah State University - Logan, UT August 2013 to May 2019

Minor in Anthropology

Utah State University - Logan, UT May 2019

Summary

Full stack web developer with experience in HTML, javascript, react as well as experience outside the web development field in anthropology, psychology, science such as biology and chemistry, as well as experience in sales, customer service, art/ceramics and many other fields.

Technical Skills & Certificates (links to certifications)

HTML5, NoSQL, MongoDB, Handlebars, Javascript ES6+, Github, Express, ¡Query, CSS3, Git, React, Bootstrap, SQL, MySQL, Node, Firebase, Oauth2

Applications & Projects

- React Portfolio React portfolio project
- R-o-u-t-e-s MERN SPA Capstone Project
- Note Taker Note taking application

Work Experience

Rover Dog daycare & grooming assistant

Kamas, UT - May 2017 to present

- · Grew a successful small business with over 30 clients within few months time
- Accumulated a 5 star customer satisfaction rate with over ten profile reviews
- · Maintained long term customers using high quality communication services, photo updates, and quick response time

Sales and Leasing **Specialist**

Ken Garff Automotive Group -Salt Lake City, UT - May 2019 to April 2020

- Increased individual sales progressively each month by 20%
- · Collaborated with a team of 15 people to increase departments sales above goals consistently each month
- · Created returning clients and lifetime customers by using quality service and communication skills

Full-Time Sales/Stock Associate

Michael Kors, Park City - May 2016 to August 2018

- Created innovative backroom organization for quick refilling and easy inventory management of new products
- · Each month I individually sold between 30-40% of the stores monthly sales
- Top 3 in sales performance every month throughout my two vears at the store
- · Created displays to increase the sales of both new and old product in the store